Rogelio Antonio Pérez Díaz

Computer Systems Engineer.

Profile

I have knowledge in software development, my main focus has been server-side programming using languages like Java, Javascript and PHP. I have worked with frameworks such as Laravel, Node and PrimeFaces to speed up software development times.

Experience

Web Developer @ DSW Diseño y Soluciones Web

February 2021 - July 2021

- Requirements gathering of software whit different clients.
- Creation of UML diagrams.
- Development and programing of web applications working with different programming languages and frameworks such as HMTL, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and Laravel.
- Deployment of web applications to servers.

Web Developer @ INSTITUTO TECNOLOGICO DE TOLUCA

January 2020 - August 2020

- Development of web application aimed at raising awareness of the preservation of the environment.
- Development and programing using PHP, Laravel and JavaScript.
- Web layout using Bootstrap Studio, HTLM and CSS.
- Creation of unit and features tests created with PHPUnit.

Web developer @ BANDGRAM (Personal Project)

April 2019 - January 2020

- Development of web application focus on help the diffusion of indie artists.
- Programming of API REST services using Laravel.
- APIS tests using Postman.
- Implementation API REST services using Ajax and JavaScript.
- Development and design of the site using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

Education

INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO DE TOLUCA

August 2016 - July 2021.

Computer Systems Engineer with Specialty in Technologies for the Development of Mobile Applications.

Skills and abilities

Initiative to work in team, logicalmathematical reasoning, sense of urgency and responsibility to reach objectives, collective property.

Programming Languages

CSS, Dart, HTML, JavaScript, Java, PHP, SQL

Libraries and Frameworks

Bootstrap, Flutter, jQuery, Laravel, Node, PrimeFaces, React

Databases

MongoDB, MySql, Oracle, PostgreSql

Tools and Platforms

Composer, Babel, Digital Ocean, Firebase, Git, Heroku, Npm, Postman, Webpack